[Music]
[Música]
uh I know there's been a bit of a stir these days
eh yo sé que habido movida estos días
for mentioning Javid Speaking
por haber mencionado javid Hablando
clearly but I'm going to take it as a source
claro pero lo voy a [__] como fuente
just to contradict you
solamente por llevaros la contraria
because today FJ showed him with him Okay
porque hoy ha mostrado FJ con él Bueno
but let's see the information and on the
pero para vamos a ver la información e
Anabel Pantoja issue let's
del tema de Anabel Pantoja vamos a
comment Simply because it seems like there are
comentar Simplemente porque se parece
lawsuits that are going
ser que hay demandas que van salía
ahead against YouTube channels no and
adelante contra canales de youtuber no y
we were like speculating [ __ ]
estábamos como especulando [__]
How many channels will there be 10 will be such and I
Cuántos canales serán 10 serán tal y He
discovered a channel here today I mean m I
descubierto hoy aquí un canal O sea m
think it exceeds Juanca's level
creo que supera el nivel de de juanca
with that I'll tell you everything FJ m clear here we
con eso te lo digo todo FJ m claro aquí
already have a candidate that I didn't know about
ya tenemos un candidato que yo no sabía
okay very strong demand from Anabel
vale muy fuerte demando de Anabel
Pantoja the YouTubers let's see she
Pantoja los youtuber a ver ella a lo
maybe can sue whatever she wants but she's
mejor puede demandar lo que quiera pero
not going to focus on YouTubers that maybe you
no se va a centrar en youtuber que a lo
know more than those of us who are
mejor conocéis más de los que estamos
here it's not always going to be like this I want you to
aquí siempre no va a ser así quiero que
see screen this YouTuber is going to fall
veáis pantalla este youtuber va a caer
Yes or yes And it's the next one I'm going to put it
Sí o sí Y es el siguiente lo voy a poner
like this so you can see it better Look here
así para que lo veáis mejor Mirad aquí
is a channel okay Here is mine
está un canal vale Aquí está el mío
I want you to look  the LoL lolol medium
quiero que miréis el medio LoL lolol
here what LoL lolol didn't know It's not
aquí lo que LoL lolol no conocía No es
that I didn't know this channel but it's that you really
que no conocía este canal pero es que
wanted to disconnect you really wanted you really
fuerte quisiste desconectar quisiste
wanted to disconnect your daughter so they would
quisiste desconectar a tu hija para que
n't find your friend's semen really
no encontrasen el semen de tu amigo muy
hard uncle Fer ferte What the [ __ ] But I've
fuerte tío Fer ferte Qué [__] Pero
never seen this in my life eh But
esto no lo he visto en la vida eh Pero
you know what's happening that what
sabes qué pasa que que quié fuerte qué
really strong what happened this looks like it's one of those channels that appears and then disappears you know and you go know who the [ __ ] who the [ __ ] it is Let's see you ask Google and I understand that if it's monetized it's taken out eh Look you're guilty and you've lied in every statement that you've done
en cada declaración que que has hecho
tap favor and reveal his Secret with David we ca
tap favor y revela su Secreto con David
n't keep seeing each other secretly
no podemos seguir viéndonos a escondidas
but my goodness How mother where does it say that the [ __ ] that in the
pero madre mía Cómo madre dónde pone eso
end up there where
[__] que lo al final ahí arriba donde
Chabelita is up we can't keep
está Chabelita arriba no podemos seguir
watching hidden Pantoja cheats on her
viendo escondido Pantoja engaa a su
cousin Nabel and her husband to rf I mean it's really
prima nabel y su marido a rf o sea es
hard but but well the only
puerte fuerte pero pero bueno la única
drugged up one is you Because of you my
drogad dista eres tú Por tu culpa mi
son my daughter did that merchi fight I mean  he
hijo mi hija hizo eso pelea de merchi o
invents to take it up the ass but there
sea se inventa a tomar por culo pero que
are
son
18000 my goodness all the videos last
18000 madre mía todos los vídeos duran
18 minutes But this What is 5 years
18 minutazos Pero esto Qué es 5 años
little for criminals like you that's why
poco para criminales como vosotros por
also and how are the videos, I mean
eso también y cómo son los vídeos o sea
if you enter mer betrays his daughter Anabel
si entras mer traiciona a su hija Anabel
David is innocent the only guilty one is
David es inocente la única culpable es
for being drugged man but but but what a
por ir drogada tío pero pero pero qué
barbarity is this but part that
barbaridad es esto pero parte que
neither that channel is still a voice
tampoco ese canal todavía es una voz
cona and they are images passing FJ or so this this of
cona y son imágenes pasando FJ o sea
course you have to ask
esto esto claro tienes que pedirle a
Google to identify the person
Google que te identifique a la persona
that of course well being the data of
que claro pues siando los datos de
adsense and others because of course in adsense
adsense y demás porque Claro en adsens
you have had your data to be able to
te has tenido tus datos para poder
monetize of course of course if you are
monetizar Claro claro si estás
monetizing you have to yes or yes give data
monetizando tienes que sí o sí da datos
but now that that one from Spain no that is
pero ahora que esa de España no esa es
another
otra
No look at this You are fired
No mira este Estás despedida prostituta
cheap prostitute For God's sake You are going to fall like a rat
barata Por Dios Vais a caer como rata le
the judge says Isabel Pantoja I am going to
dice el juez Isabel Pantoja me voy a
keep the [ __ ] girl Look look look at
quedar con la niña zorra Mira mira mira
this Anabel Pantoja loses custody of
este Anabel Pantoja pierde la custura de
her daughter and says isapi I am going to keep
su hija y le dice isapi me voy a quedar
the [ __ ] girl abusive
con la niña zorra maltratadora
LoL  eh
LoL eh
this channel is not
este canal por no está
closed nobody has reported this man
cerrado nadie ha reportado esto tío
how many people does it have How many subscribers does it have they
cuánta gente tiene Cuántos suscriptores
opened it there pi 31000 but you
tiene lo abrieron por ahí pí 31000 pero
know what it is we can't know but
sabes qué es que no podemos saber pero
surely this is a channel that
seguramente esto sea un canal que
existed before and has changed the
existiese antes y le ha cambiado el
name no well August 2 eh August 2 do you
nombre no bueno 2 de Agosto eh 2 de
think August already has 3000 my god I'm
creas de agosto ya tiene 3000 madre mía
going to start inventing news
me voy a poner a inventar yo noticias
No no yes yes yes yes let's go
No
I don't know with
no sí sí sí sí vamos me meto no sé con
Los Reyes Chinos For example I don't know or
Los Reyes chinos Por ejemplo yo que sé o
with Putin or I don't know here the fat one is
con el Putin o no sé aquí la gorda eres
you are suns exploding against Pilar Vidal
tú son soles explota contra Pilar Vidal
my god and whoever has the most views
madre mía y el que tenga más visitas
has to be an outrage Because
tiene que ser una barbaridad Porque
these are the old ones no well more
estos son los viejos no pues más
outrageous than Anabel's that one about the
barbaridad que la de Anabel esa de lo
friend is outrageous Well look there are
del amigo manda narices Pues mira hay
some that have the taste of Kiko Rivera
algunos que tienen oaz de Kiko Rivera me
ruined my life you son of a [ __ ] Kiko Rivera
aruno la vida hija de [__] Kiko Rivera
his mother Irene Rosales dapa
su madre Irene Rosales dapa
Kiko's biological father You are a
el padre biológico de Kiko Eres una [__]
fat [ __ ] and Antonio Marto Cristina goyan
gorda e Antonio Marto Cristina goyan
mother m but how strong Because  the one of you are one the one
madre m pero qu fuerte Porque el de eres
of Caritina Goyanes You are a
una el de la caritina goyanes Eres una
fat [ __ ] It's when the girl dies it does
[__] gorda Es cuando fallece la muchacha
n't
no
make it very strong eh [ __ ] It is that it
hace que es muy fuerte eh [__] Es que
is very strong eh my goodness But the
es muy fuerte eh madre mía Pero a la
person who carries that is worth it
persona que lleva eso le merece la pena
because I don't know, he has to have a
porque no sé tiene que tener una una
lawsuit, that one does have to have a
demanda ese sí que tiene que tener
lawsuit, that one there yes I say he has it
demanda esa ahí sí que digo yo la tiene
C Look, I don't know if it's worth it but
C Mira no sé si a le merece la pena pero
that there are 160,000 sick people
que haya 160.000 enfermitos
eh watching that video what can I tell you for
eh viendo ese vídeo qué te digo par
16,000 people who have seen that video, of course
16000 personas han visto ese vídeo claro
the problem is who sees it, who
es que el problema es quién lo ve quién
consumes it, that misinformation
lo consume que está la desinformación
is the order of the day because Of course if
está la orden del día porque Claro si la
people do nothing, they say that the video is
gente no hace nada dice que el vídeo es
outrageous, they give their opinion, dislike And that, the
una barbaridad opina dislike Y eso el
video goes up, it's not even
vídeo sube para arriba ni siquiera es
misinformation FJ what
desinformación FJ que
misinformation just seeing the title you
desinformación solo ver el título ya
know that it is, it's a lie, let's
sabes que es que es mentira
see what they give Dani vital we know
todo a ver que dan Dani vital sabemos
that he makes up half or more of it but
que se inventa la mitad o más de la pero
not that much nonsense eh And even if he says it,
no tanta burrada eh Y aunque la diga
my goodness, what outrageousness t crazy
madre mía qué barbaridad t una locura
crazy  tremendous but well that's
una locura tremendo pero bueno es que es
what I'm telling you, I mean normally they are
lo que te digo o sea normalmente son
like channels that are
como canales que se quedan en el en el
forgotten because they are anonymous and after a while they
olvido porque son anónimos y al tiempo
disappear or whatever I don't know or nobody
desaparecen o lo que sea no sé o nadie
touches them it's very complicated I don't know
les mete mano es muy complicado no sé
but
pero
well than
bueno than